Think this is what they do all day?
The Secret Life of Pets is a family, comedy,
adventure film directed by Chris Renaud.
The quiet life of a terrier named Max is upended when his owner
takes in Duke, a stray whom Max instantly dislikes.
Max (voice), played by Louis C.K..
Duke (voice), played by Eric Stonestreet.
Snowball (voice), played by Kevin Hart.
Gidget (voice), played by Jenny Slate.
Katie (voice), played by Ellie Kemper.
Tiberius (voice), played by Albert Brooks.
The Secret Life of Pets is a 2016 American animated comedy film directed by
Chris Renaud and written by Brian Lynch, Cinco Paul and Ken Daurio.
Produced by Illumination Entertainment and distributed by Universal Pictures, the film stars the voices of Louis C.K., Eric Stonestreet,
Jenny Slate, Kevin Hart, Ellie Kemper, Lake Bell, Dana Carvey, Hannibal Buress, Bobby Moynihan, Steve Coogan, and Albert Brooks.
Taking place in New York City, the film's plot follows the relationship between
a spoiled terrier named Max and a giant, unruly dog named Duke.
It also follows what other pets do when their owners are gone for the day.
The Secret Life of Pets premiered at the Annecy International Animated Film Festival on
June 16, 2016, and was released in theaters in the United States on July 8.
The film received generally positive reviews and grossed $885.3 million worldwide, making it the
sixth-highest-grossing film of 2016 as well as the year's most profitable release.
A sequel, The Secret Life of Pets 2, was released on June 7, 2019, with
Patton Oswalt taking over the role of Max from Louis C.K.
The film explores themes of bunny, pet, anthropomorphism, dog, animals.
The tone is lighthearted.